<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Turing Gibberish v2</string>
    <string name="app_details">here should be app details</string>
    <string name="paragraph">A well-organized paragraph supports or develops a single controlling idea, which is expressed in a sentence called the topic sentence. A topic sentence has several important functions: it substantiates or supports an essay’s thesis statement; it unifies the content of a paragraph and directs the order of the sentences; and it advises the reader of the subject to be discussed and how the paragraph will discuss it. Readers generally look to the first few sentences in a paragraph to determine the subject and perspective of the paragraph. That’s why it’s often best to put the topic sentence at the very beginning of the paragraph. In some cases, however, it’s more effective to place another sentence before the topic sentence—for example, a sentence linking the current paragraph to the previous one, or one providing background information.</string>

    <string name="discription">Turing Gibberish is an Android application for encrypting/Decrypting data using Caesar cipher. Caesar shift, is one of the simplest and most widely known encryption techniques.The present age is the age of information, so information security is very important. You write down your confidential information somewhere, so anyone can easily see it. Encrypted data from it can be easily returned using a single key. When you receive an encrypted data from someone, you will need the correct key.These apps have a simple interface that anyone can use.</string>
    <string name="main_page">Main Page Devided by Two part, Input part and Output part. In input part, Your need Two item(Original text or Cipher text and key). one more thing you need to know: Encryption or Decryption. When you input a original text and Key then you need to select engryption or decryption then click on finger_Print icon then your text will be cipher text also called as Secure text. Then you can copy the output or you will be able to crate a txt file to save your secure data. or you can sheare it on any platform. On the other side you already had a cipher data to convert it plain text. you need to know private key. when you enter right key and select decryption then you get plain text. otherwise you will get wrong information.</string>
    <string name="intro_animation">For intro animation we used LOTTIE Animation. In gradle file we import a package and In xml, wrote lottieAnimationView. Inside LottieAnimationView used some attribute like( autoPlay, elevation). After this in java file, we used a handler for delay and go to next page. In intro animation we used a simple animation for text. actually its a image and we gave it a motion.</string>
    <string name="introduction">After intro animation, automaticlly open a page(Introduction page). Top of introduction page, we used a image (Logo image). Its completely diffrent from main logo. Under the logo, used a LinearLayout. Inside this linear layout we used a Header Text, a introduction text, and two button. a about button and a Next button. When you clicked on about button it will came back this page and next button move on Main page. Here we give a smart logic. if you clicked on Next button then you will go Main page otherwise after 10 secend, auto you will move into Main Page.</string>
</resources>